Map quizData = {
  "Vegetables Quiz": {
    "Level 1": [
      {
        'question':
            'This green, leafy vegetable is often used as a base for salads and sandwiches. What is it?',
        'options': ['Cucumber', 'Lettuce', 'Spinach', 'Kale'],
        'answer': 'Lettuce',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is commonly orange and known for its high beta-carotene content. What is it?',
        'options': ['Broccoli', 'Carrot', 'Cauliflower', 'Radish'],
        'answer': 'Carrot',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'Often used in Italian cuisine, this vegetable is a key ingredient in making sauces. What is it?',
        'options': ['Onion', 'Tomato', 'Bell Pepper', 'Zucchini'],
        'answer': 'Tomato',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable belongs to the onion family and has a strong, distinct flavor. What is it?',
        'options': ['Garlic', 'Shallot', 'Ginger', 'Leek'],
        'answer': 'Garlic',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'It\'s a cruciferous vegetable, green in color, and often associated with being a good source of vitamin C. What is it?',
        'options': ['Cabbage', 'Cauliflower', 'Spinach', 'Broccoli'],
        'answer': 'Broccoli',
      },
    ],
    "Level 2": [
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is small, round, and comes in various colors like red, yellow, and green. What are they?',
        'options': ['Cherry tomatoes', 'Bell peppers', 'Radishes', 'Cucumbers'],
        'answer': 'Cherry tomatoes',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable has a long, cylindrical shape and is often used in salads and coleslaw. What is it?',
        'options': ['Carrot', 'Zucchini', 'Celery', 'Cucumber'],
        'answer': 'Cucumber',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'It\'s a green, leafy vegetable often used in salads and sandwiches. Popeye loves it. What is it?',
        'options': ['Kale', 'Spinach', 'Lettuce', 'Swiss chard'],
        'answer': 'Spinach',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is known for its distinctive, peppery taste and is often used in salads. What is it?',
        'options': ['Radish', 'Arugula', 'Cilantro', 'Basil'],
        'answer': 'Arugula',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'It\'s a root vegetable, commonly white or yellow, and used in various culinary dishes. What is it?',
        'options': ['Sweet potato', 'Onion', 'Potato', 'Turnip'],
        'answer': 'Potato',
      },
    ],
    "Level 3": [
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is often used in stir-fries and has a long, slender shape. What is it?',
        'options': ['Eggplant', 'Asparagus', 'Green beans', 'Okra'],
        'answer': 'Green beans',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'It\'s a round, purple vegetable often used in Mediterranean cuisine and pizza. What is it?',
        'options': ['Eggplant', 'Artichoke', 'Cabbage', 'Avocado'],
        'answer': 'Eggplant',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is often used in Indian cuisine, known for its distinctive, bulbous shape. What is it?',
        'options': ['Cauliflower', 'Turnip', 'Radish', 'Ginger'],
        'answer': 'Cauliflower',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'It\'s a leafy green vegetable with a slightly bitter taste, often used in salads and sandwiches. What is it?',
        'options': [
          'Romaine lettuce',
          'Iceberg lettuce',
          'Kale',
          'Swiss chard'
        ],
        'answer': 'Romaine lettuce',
      },
      {
        'question':
            'This vegetable is small, round, and red, often used in salads and as a garnish. What is it?',
        'options': ['Cherry tomato', 'Radish', 'Grape tomato', 'Plum tomato'],
        'answer': 'Cherry tomato',
      },
    ],
    "Level 4": [
      {
        "question":
            "Which vegetable is rich in vitamin C and often used in salads?",
        "options": ["Cucumber", "Bell Pepper", "Spinach", "Tomato"],
        "answer": "Bell Pepper"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What vegetable is the primary ingredient in the Middle Eastern dish 'Hummus'?",
        "options": ["Chickpea", "Eggplant", "Tomato", "Cucumber"],
        "answer": "Chickpea"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which vegetable is commonly used to make a classic French soup called 'Vichyssoise'?",
        "options": ["Leek", "Potato", "Carrot", "Onion"],
        "answer": "Leek"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which vegetable is commonly used to make the Italian dish 'Ratatouille'?",
        "options": ["Zucchini", "Eggplant", "Bell Pepper", "Tomato"],
        "answer": "Zucchini"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which vegetable is also known as 'Lady's Finger'?",
        "options": ["Okra", "Asparagus", "Green Bean", "Zucchini"],
        "answer": "Okra"
      },
    ],
    "Level 5": [
      {
        "question":
            "What vegetable is commonly used to make the Mexican dish 'Guacamole'?",
        "options": ["Avocado", "Tomato", "Onion", "Cilantro"],
        "answer": "Avocado"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which vegetable is known for its deep purple color and is often used to make a popular dip?",
        "options": ["Eggplant", "Beetroot", "Cabbage", "Purple Cabbage"],
        "answer": "Beetroot"
      },
      {
        "question": "What vegetable, when fermented, becomes sauerkraut?",
        "options": ["Cabbage", "Carrot", "Cucumber", "Radish"],
        "answer": "Cabbage"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which vegetable, known for its bitterness, is often blanched before cooking?",
        "options": ["Broccoli", "Cauliflower", "Asparagus", "Brussels Sprouts"],
        "answer": "Brussels Sprouts"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What coniferous vegetable, often served raw in salads, has a distinctive peppery taste?",
        "options": ["Cabbage", "Arugula", "Kale", "Radish"],
        "answer": "Radish"
      },
    ],
    "Level 6": [],
    "Level 7": [],
    "Level 8": [],
    "Level 9": [],
    "Level 10": [],
  },
  "Math Quiz": {
    "Level 1": [],
    "Level 2": [],
    "Level 3": [],
    "Level 4": [],
    "Level 5": [],
    "Level 6": [],
    "Level 7": [],
    "Level 8": [],
    "Level 9": [],
    "Level 10": [],
  },
  "Technology Quiz": {
    "Level 1": [
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: An electronic, digital or computer device that outputs a video signal or visual image to display a video game.",
        "options": ["Game console", "Laptop", "Bluetooth speaker", "Tablet"],
        "answer": "Game console"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A head-mounted device that provides virtual reality for the wearer.",
        "options": [
          "Game console",
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Virtual reality headset",
          "Laptop"
        ],
        "answer": "Virtual reality headset"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A wireless speaker capable of receiving audio signals over Bluetooth connections.",
        "options": [
          "Virtual reality headset",
          "Action camera",
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Smartwatch"
        ],
        "answer": "Bluetooth speaker"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A digital camera designed for recording action while being immersed in it.",
        "options": [
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Game console",
          "Action camera",
          "Smartwatch"
        ],
        "answer": "Action camera"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A mobile electronic device designed primarily for reading digital e-books and periodicals.",
        "options": ["Laptop", "E-reader", "Drone", "Virtual reality headset"],
        "answer": "E-reader"
      },
    ],
    "Level 2": [
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A portable device that combines mobile telephone and computing functions.",
        "options": ["Laptop", "Game console", "Smartphone", "Drone"],
        "answer": "Smartphone"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A small, portable personal computer with a screen and alphanumeric keyboard.",
        "options": [
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Virtual reality headset",
          "Tablet",
          "Laptop"
        ],
        "answer": "Laptop"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A mobile device, typically with a mobile operating system and touchscreen display, larger than a smartphone.",
        "options": [
          "Tablet",
          "Drone",
          "Virtual reality headset",
          "Game console"
        ],
        "answer": "Tablet"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: An unmanned aerial vehicle that can be remotely controlled or fly autonomously through software-controlled flight plans.",
        "options": [
          "Virtual reality headset",
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Action camera",
          "Drone"
        ],
        "answer": "Drone"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "What device is described as: A wearable computing device that resembles a wristwatch or other time-keeping device.",
        "options": [
          "Smartwatch",
          "Game console",
          "Bluetooth speaker",
          "Smartphone"
        ],
        "answer": "Smartwatch"
      },
    ],
    "Level 3": [],
    "Level 4": [],
    "Level 5": [],
    "Level 6": [],
    "Level 7": [],
    "Level 8": [],
    "Level 9": [],
    "Level 10": [],
  },
  "Alphabet Quiz": {
    "Level 1": [
      {
        "question":
            "Which letter is placed wrongly in the sequence: I J K O L?",
        "options": ["N", "O", "P", "Q"],
        "answer": "O"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: L N P ...?",
        "options": ["Q", "R", "S", "T"],
        "answer": "R"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: M O Q ...?",
        "options": ["R", "S", "T", "U"],
        "answer": "S"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which letter is placed wrongly in the sequence: W R S T U?",
        "options": ["V", "W", "X", "Y"],
        "answer": "W"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter comes before P in reverse alphabetical order?",
        "options": ["M", "N", "O", "P"],
        "answer": "O"
      },
    ],
    "Level 2": [
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: E G I ...?",
        "options": ["J", "K", "L", "M"],
        "answer": "K"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter comes before N in reverse alphabetical order?",
        "options": ["K", "L", "M", "N"],
        "answer": "M"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which letter does not belong: Q L M O?",
        "options": ["N", "P", "Q", "R"],
        "answer": "Q"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: S U W ...?",
        "options": ["X", "Y", "Z", "["],
        "answer": "Y"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which letter is placed wrongly in the sequence: A B G C D?",
        "options": ["F", "G", "H", "I"],
        "answer": "G"
      },
    ],
    "Level 3": [
      {
        "question": "What letter comes before G in reverse alphabetical order?",
        "options": ["D", "E", "F", "G"],
        "answer": "F"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which letter is placed wrongly in the sequence: D E I F G?",
        "options": ["H", "I", "J", "K"],
        "answer": "I"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: T V X ...?",
        "options": ["Y", "Z", "[", "\\"],
        "answer": "Z"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter comes before M in reverse alphabetical order?",
        "options": ["J", "K", "L", "M"],
        "answer": "L"
      },
      {
        "question":
            "Which letter is placed wrongly in the sequence: K L M P N?",
        "options": ["O", "P", "Q", "R"],
        "answer": "P"
      },
    ],
    "Level 4": [
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: K M O ...?",
        "options": ["P", "Q", "R", "S"],
        "answer": "Q"
      },
      {
        "question": "What letter completes the pattern: I K M ...?",
        "options": ["N", "O", "P", "Q"],
        "answer": "O"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which letter does not belong: Z V W X?",
        "options": ["U", "Y", "Z", "["],
        "answer": "Z"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which letter does not belong: O J K M?",
        "options": ["L", "N", "O", "P"],
        "answer": "O"
      }
    ],
    "Level 5": [],
    "Level 6": [],
    "Level 7": [],
    "Level 8": [],
    "Level 9": [],
    "Level 10": [],
  },
};
